<resources>
    <string name="app_name">A.R.ViewFinder</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>

    <string name="minimum_password">Password too short, enter minimum 6 characters</string>
    <string name="auth_failed">Authentication failed, check your credentials or sign up</string>

    <!-- Introduction Slider -->
    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="skip">SKIP</string>
    <string name="start">GOT IT</string>

    <string name="slide1heading">A.R ViewFinder</string>
    <string name="slide1message">Is a geo location based augmented reality application submitted as partial fulfilment of the Newcastle University MSc E-Business (Information Systems) degree.</string>

    <string name="slide2heading">G.P.S</string>
    <string name="slide2message">Using sensors embedded in the mobile device and satellites in space, the application calculates GPS co-ordinates to pin point a users location and</string>

    <string name="slide3heading">A.R</string>
    <string name="slide3message">overlays geo-location specific information of real world objects at the users current position and surroundings over a camera view</string>

    <string name="slide4heading">Data</string>
    <string name="slide4message">from external service providers in real-time from their respective data servers such as Urban Observatory who have deployed a range of sensors around the city that record various conditions.</string>

    <string name="temperatureStatus">Temperature (Default)</string>
    <string name="humidityStatus">Humidity</string>
    <string name="soundStatus">Sound</string>
    <string name="pressureStatus">Pressure</string>
    <string name="attractionStatus">Attractions</string>
    <string name="universityStatus">University Buildings</string>
    <string name="foodStatus">Fast Food or Restaurants</string>
    <string name="title_activity_questionnaire">Questionnaire</string>

    <!-- questionnaire -->
    <string name="intro_text">
        "Introduction.\n\n"

        "Once again I would like to thank you for taking part in the review of this prototype."
        "My name is Masitano Sichone and I am pursuing a Masters degree in E-Business (Information Systems) and "
        "the prototype that you have just used is part of the artefact's of my dissertation. \n\n"
        "The survey seeks the views of everyday people with regards to Augmented Reality as a technology, "
        "the dissemination of digital information from providers to consumers and the issues and challenges faced in doing so. \n\n"
        "The results of the survey will make a great contribution towards both academia and industry and you are encouraged to "
        "respond to all the questions to the best of your knowledge bearing in mind that your responses are confidential and will be anonymized. \n\n"
        "Access to the survey and any other application data is restricted to the researcher and supervision team. \n\n"
        "Please feel free to contact me on m.k.p.sichone2@newcastle.ac.uk for any questions or comments. \n\n "
    </string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

</resources>
